Narrator: 1
Speaker: The busiest shopping street in Europe is Oxford Street.
Although numbers dropped during the Covid-19 pandemic, seventy-two thousand
shoppers a day still visit the street in the centre of London.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: The biggest railway station in the world is Grand Central Terminal in New York.
It has forty-four platforms, and covers nearly two hundred thousand square metres.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: The tallest cathedral in the world is Ulm Münster in Germany.
It is a hundred and sixty-one metres tall.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: The oldest bridge in Europe is the Arkadiko Bridge in Greece.
People still use it today. It was built more than three thousand years ago.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: The longest river in the world is the Nile.
It’s six thousand six hundred and fifty kilometres long
and goes through eleven different African countries.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: The most dangerous road in the world is Bayburt D-nine-one-five in Türkiye.
The one hundred and six-kilometre road is very high up and the weather is often foggy and rainy.
Even really good drivers find driving extremely difficult.